Guide to the Samuel L. Clemens Papers, 1796-1984 (bulk 1853-1909)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series B. Samuel L. Clemens Correspondence To Family Members
  - "Dear Charley…" Branford, 9 July 1881 (4.32 [B.201])
  - Letter to unidentified correspondent, Branford, 19 July 1881 (4.33 [B.202])
  - "Dear Charley…" Elmira, 12 Aug 1881 (4.34 [B.203])
  - "Dear Charley…", 17 Aug 1881 (4.35 [B.204])
  - "Dear Charley…" Elmira, 23 Aug 1881 (4.36 [B.205])
  - "Dear Charley…", 1881 (4.37 [B.206])
  - Telegram to [Charles] L. Webster at residence of S.L. Clemens, 26 Aug 1881 (4.38 [B.207])
  - Letter to unidentified correspondent, Aug 1881 (4.39 [B.208])
  - "Dear Charley…" Elmira, 31 Aug 1881 (4.40 [B.209])
  - "Dear Charley…" Elmira, 4 Sep 1881 (4.41 [B.210])
  - Elmira - Telegram to C.L. Webster, 6 Sep 1881 (4.42 [B.211])
  - Elmira - Telegram for Mr. Webster at residence of S.L. Clemens, 7 Sept 1881 (4.43 [B.212 ])
  - "Dear Charley…" Elmira, 7 Sep 1881 (4.44 [B.213])
  - "Dear Charley…" Elmira, 9 Sep 1881 (4.45 [B.214])
  - "Dear Charley…"C.J. Langdon, Elmira, NY, 17 Sep 1881 (4.46 [B.215])
  - Dear Charley - Find Louis C. Tiffany's present address/ Elmira, Louis C. Tiffany Esq., 19 Sep 1881 (4.47 [B.216])
  - "Dear Ma…" Elmira, 19 Sep 1881 (4.48 [B.217])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 2 Oct 1881 (4.49 [B.218])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 7 Oct 1881 (4.50 [B.219])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 10 Oct 1881 (4.51 [B.220])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, Monday, Oct 1881 (4.52 [B.221])
  - "Dear Charley…" (Imp re/typesetting machine), 25 Oct 1881 (4.53 [B.222])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 26 Oct 1881 (4.54 [B.223])
  - "My Dear Bro...", 26 Oct 1881 (4.55 [B.224])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 28 Oct 1881 (4.56 [B.225])
  - "My Dear Bro…" Hartford, 11 Nov 1881 (4.57 [B.226])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 15 Nov 1881 (4.58 [B.227])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 17 Nov 1881 (4.59 [B.228])
  - Boston - Letter to SLC from R.K. Ticknor, 18 Nov 1881 (4.60 [B.229])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 19 Nov 1881 (4.61 [B.230])
  - "My Dear Bro…" Hartford, 21 Nov 1881 (4.62 [B.231])
  - Hartford - Telegram for [Charles] L. Webster, 22 Nov 1881 (4.63 [B.232])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 24 Nov 1881 (4.64 [B.233])
  - "Dear Charley…" Montreal, 27 Nov 1881 (4.65 [B.234])
  - Letter from Olivia L. Clemens, 23 Dec 1881 (4.66 [B.235])
  - "Dear Charley…", 31 Dec, 1881 (4.67 [B.236])
  - "Dear Sister…", 8 Dec 1881 (4.68 [B.237])
  - "Dear Charley…", 2 Jan 1882 (5.1 [B.238])
  - "Dear Charley…", 5 Jan 1882 (5.2 [B.239])
  - "Dear Charley…", 10 Jan 1882 (5.3 [B.240])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, Jan 21, 1882 (5.4 [B.241])
  - "Dear Charlie…" Hartford, 20 Mar 1882; (typed) (5.5 [B.242])
  - "Dear Charlie…" Hartford, 20 Mar 1882; (typed) (5.6 [B.243])
  - "Dear Charlie…" Hartford, 27 Mar 1882; (typed) (5.7 [B.244])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 12 Apr 1882 (5.8 [B.245])
  - "Dear Charlie…" Hartford, 17 Apr 1882; (typed) (5.9 [B.246])
  - "Dear Charlie…" Hartford, 30 Apr 1882; (typed) (5.10 [B.247])
  - "My Dear Mother…" Farmington Ave., Hartford, 29 May 1882 (5.11 [B.248])
  - "Dear Charley…", 12 June 1882 (5.12 [B.249])
  - "Dear Charley…", 5 June 1882 (5.13 [B.250])
  - "Dear Charlie…" Hartford, 15 June 1882; (typed) (5.14 [B.251])
  - Telegram to [Charles] L. Webster. Hartford, 17 June 1882 (5.15 [B.252])
  - "Dear Charlie…" Hartford, 8 July 1882; (typed) (5.16 [B.253])
  - "Dear Charley…", 26 June 1882 (5.17 [B.254])
  - "Dear Charley…", ? 21, [1882] (5.18 [B.255])
  - "Dear Charley…" Elmira, Sunday, July 1882 (5.19 [B.256])
  - "Dear Charley…", 8 July 1882 (5.20 [B.257])
  - "Dear Charlie…" Hartford, 11 July1882; (typed) (5.21 [B.258])
  - "Dear Charley…" Elmira, 18 July 1882 (5.22 [B.259])
  - "Dear Charley…" Elmira, 25 July 1882 (5.23 [B.260])
  - "Dear Charley…" Elmira, 26 July 1882 (5.24 [B.261])
  - "Dear Charley…" Elmira, 1 Aug 1882 (5.25 [B.262])
  - "Dear Charley…" Elmira, 8 Aug 1882 (5.26 [B.263])
  - "Dear Charley…", 14 Apr 1882 (5.27 [B.264])
  - "Dear Charley…" Elmira, 9 Aug 1882 (5.28 [B.265])
  - "Dear Charley…", 12 Aug 1882 (5.29 [B.266])
  - "Dear Charley…" Elmira, 15 Aug 1882 (5.30 [B.267])
  - Telegram to [Charles] L. Webster, Elmira, 20 Aug 1882 (5.31 [B.268])
  - "Dear Annie…" Elmira, 29 Aug 1882 (5.32 [B.269])
  - "My Dear Brother…" Fredonia, NY, 30 Aug 1882 (5.33 [B.270])
  - "Dear Charley…", 9 Sep 1882 (5.34 [B.271])
  - [Charles] L. Webster, K Engraving Co. Telegram from SLC, Sep 1882 (5.35 [B.272])
  - "Dear Charley…" Elmira, 2 Sep 1882 (5.36 [B.273])
  - "Dear Charley…", 19 Sep 1882 (5.37 [B.274])
  - Elmira, NY-Telegram to [Charles] Webster, 24 Sep 1882 (5.38 [B.275])
  - "Dear Charley…" Elmira, 19 Sep 1882 (5.39 [B.276])
  - "Dear Charley…" Elmira, Sunday, 24 Sep 1882 (5.40 [B.277])
  - To James R. Osgood, Boston, 1882 (5.41 [B.278])
  - "Dear Charley…", 6 Oct 1882 (5.42 [B.279])
  - "Dear Charlie…" Hartford, 9 Oct 1882; (typed) (5.43 [B.280])
  - "Dear Charlie…" Hartford, 27 Oct 1882; (typed) (5.44 [B.281])
  - "Dear Charlie…" Hartford, 21 Oct 1882; (typed) (5.45 [B.282])
  - "Dear Charlie…" Hartford, 30 Oct 1882; (typed) (5.46 [B.283])
  - "Dear Charlie…" Hartford, 30 Oct 1882; (typed) (5.47 [B.284])
  - "Dear Charlie…" Hartford, 11 Nov 1882; (typed) (5.48 [B.285])
  - County Clerk Archer County Texas- Letter to S.L. Clemens, 14 Nov 1882 (5.49 [B.286 ])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 21 Nov 1882 (5.50 [B.287])
  - "Dear Charlie…" Hartford, 25 Nov 1882; (typed) (5.51 [B.288])
  - "Dear Charley…" (5.52 [B.289])
  - "Dear Charley…", 30 Nov 1882 (5.53 [B.290])
  - "My Dear Sister…" Hartford, 20 Dec 1882; (typed) (5.54 [B.291])
  - "Dear Charlie…" Hartford, 16 Dec 1882; (typed) (5.55 [B.292])
  - "Dear Charlie…" Hartford, 30 Dec, 1882; (typed) (5.56 [B.293])
  - "My Dear Sister…" Wednesday, 1882? (5.57 [B.294])
  - "Dear Charley…" Sunday, 1882? (5.58 [B.295])
  - "Dear Charley…" Monday, 1882 (5.59 [B.296])
  - Jas. R. Osgood Co. Letter to SLC with note to Charley, 3 Jan 1883 (5.60 [B.297])
  - "Dear Charley…", 15 Jan 1883 (5.61 [B.298])
  - "Dear Charley…", Jan. 27. 1883 (5.62 [B.299])
  - "Dear Charley…", 1883 (5.63 [B.300])
  - "Dear Charlie…" Hartford, 22 Feb 1883; (typed) (5.64 [B.301])
  - "Dear Charley…" Sunday, 1883 (5.65 [B.302])
  - "Dear Charley…", 9 Mar 1883 (5.66 [B.303])
  - "Dear Charlie…" Hartford, 23 Mar 1883; (typed) (5.67 [B.304])
  - "Dear Charlie…" Hartford, 31 Mar 1883; (typed) (5.68 [B.305])
  - "Dear Charlie…" Hartford, 16 Apr 1883; (typed) (5.69 [B.306])
  - "Dear Charlie…" Hartford, 24 Apr 1883; (typed) (5.70 [B.307])
  - "Dear Charlie…" Hartford, 1 May 1883; (typed) (5.71 [B.308])
  - "Dear Charlie…" Hartford, 7 May 1883; (typed) (5.72 [B.309])
  - "Dear Charlie…" Hartford, 17 May 1883; (typed) (5.73 [B.310])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 8 June 1883 (5.74 [B.311])
  - Telegram to [Charles] L Webster, June 1883 (5.75 [B.312])
  - "Dear Charley…" Elmira, 18 June 1883 (5.76 [B.313])
  - "Dear Charley…" Elmira, 20 June 1883 (5.77 [B.314])
  - "Dear Charley…" Elmira, 29 June 1883 (6.1 [B.315])
  - "Dear Charley…" Elmira, 26 July 1883 (6.2 [B.316])
  - "Dear Charley…", 1 Aug 1883 (6.3 [B.317])
  - "Dear Charley…", 3 Aug 1883 (6.4 [B.318])
  - Memorandum, 1883 (6.5 [B.319])
  - Letter to unidentified correspondent, 6 Aug 1883 (6.6 [B.320])
  - "Dear Charley…" Elmira, 24 Aug 1883 (6.7 [B.321])
  - "Dear Charley…" Elmira, 31 Aug 1883 (6.8 [B.322])
  - "Dear Charley…" Wednesday, 1883 (6.9 [B.323])
  - "Dear Charley…" Sunday, 1883 (6.10 [B.324])
  - Memo - Charles L. Webster, Publisher, 13 Sep 1883 (6.11 [B.325])
  - "Dear Charley…" Charles L. Webster, Publisher, 3 Sep 1883 (6.12 [B.326])
  - "My Dear Mother…" Hartford, 15 Sep 1883 (6.13 [B.327])
  - "Dear Charley…" Saturday, 1883 (6.14 [B.328])
  - "Dear Charley…", 22 Sep 1883 (6.15 [B.329])
  - "My Dear Bro…", 28 Sep 1883 (6.16 [B.330])
  - "Dear Charley…" Thursday, Sept. 1883 (6.17 [B.331])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 29 Sep 1883 (6.18 [B.332])
  - "Dear Charley…", Oct. 3 or 4, 1883 (6.19 [B.333])
  - "Dear Charley…", 6 Oct 1883 (6.20 [B.334])
  - "Dear Charley…", 10 Oct 1883 (6.21 [B.335])
  - "Dear Charley…", 15 Oct 1883 (6.22 [B.336])
  - "Dear Mollie…", Late 1883? (6.23 [B.337])
  - "Dear Charlie…" Hartford, 26 Nov 1883; (typed) (6.24 [B.338])
  - Memo from Jas R. Osgood Co. to C.L. Webster, 9 Nov 1883 (6.25 [B.339])
  - "Dear Charley…", 30 Nov 1883 (6.26 [B.340])
  - Letter from Olivia Clemens, 17 Dec 1883 (6.27 [B.341])
  - "Dear Charley…", 19 Dec 1883 (6.28 [B.342])
  - "Dear Charley…", 19 Dec 1883 (6.29 [B.343])
  - "Dear Charley…", 20 Dec 1883 (6.30 [B.344])
  - "My dear Annie…", 1883 (6.31 [B.345])
  - "My Dear Sister…", 24 Dec 1883 (6.32 [B.346])
  - Telegram-Hartford to L. Webster 658 Bway NYC, 26 Dec 1883 (6.33 [B.347])
  - "Dear Charley…", 27 Dec 1883 (6.34 [B.348])
  - Notes on Mt's History Game, 1883 (6.35 [B.349])
  - "Dear Charley…", Jan 2, 1884 (6.36 [B.350])
  - "Dear Charley…", 7 Jan 1884 (6.37 [B.351])
  - "Dear Charley…" Monday, Jan. 1884 (6.38 [B.352])
  - Hartford- Letter to CLW from Olivia L. Clemens, 11 Jan 1884 (6.39 [B.353])
  - Slote check for $773 received, 17 Jan 1884 (6.40 [B.354])
  - "Dear Charley…" Sunday, 1884 (6.41 [B.355])
  - "Dear Charley…", 28 Jan 1884 (6.42 [B.356])
  - "Dear Charley…", 29 Jan 1884 (6.43 [B.357])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 8 Feb 1884 (6.44 [B.358])
  - "Dear Charley…", 18 Feb 1884 (6.45 [B.359])
  - "Dear Charley…", Feb. 29, 1884 (6.46 [B.360])
  - "Dear Charley…" Monday, 3 Mar 1884 (6.47 [B.361])
  - "Dear Charley…", 5 Mar 1884 (6.48 [B.362])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 6 Mar 1884 (6.49 [B.363])
  - "Dear Charley…", 20 Mar 1884 (6.50 [B. 364])
  - Notes on bookmaking of the period in SLC's handwriting, Mar 1884 (6.51 [B.365])
  - "Dear Charley…" Saturday Eve, Mar 1884 (6.52 [B.366])
  - "Dear Charley…", 27 Mar 1884 (6.53 [B.367])
  - Olivia L. Clemens Power of Attorney to Charles L. Webster, 8 Apr 1884 (6.54 [B.368])
  - "Dear Charley…", 12 Apr 1884 (6.55 [B.369])
  - "Dear Charley…" Monday, 14 Apr 1884 (6.56 [B.370])
  - "Dear Charley…", 15 Apr 1884 (6.57 [B.371])
  - "Dear Ma…" Hartford, 15 Apr 1884 (6.58 [B.372])
  - "Dear Charley…", 16 Apr 1884 (6.59 [B.373])
  - "Dear Charley, Show him this…", 25 Apr 1884 (6.60 [B.374])
  - "Dear Charley, Yes, I think the raft chapter…", 22 Apr 1884 (6.61 [B.375])
  - Letter from Josephine Beemer, annotated by S.L.C. for Charley, 28 Apr 1884 (6.62 [B.375a-b])
  - "Dear Charley…", 30 Apr 1884 (6.63 [B.375c])
  - "Dear Charley…", 30 Apr 1884 (6.64 [B.375d])
  - "Dear Charley…", 7 May 1884 (6.65 [B.375e])
  - Letter from W.D. Howells, annotated by S.L.C. for Charley, 10 May 1884 (6.66 [B.375f])
  - "Dear Charley…", 12 May 1884 (6.67 [B.375g])
  - "Dear Charley…", 19 May 1884 (6.68 [B.375h])
  - "Dear Charley…", 23 May 1884 (6.69 [B.375i])
  - "Dear Charley…", 24 May 1884; (copy only) (7.1 [B.375j])
  - "Dear Charley…", 31 May 1884 (7.2[B.375k])
  - "Dear Charley…", 6 June 1884 (7.3 [B.375l])
  - "Dear Charley…", Sunday, circa 6 June 1884 (7.4 [B.375m])
  - Letter from Miss Mattie Curry to SLC. Carson, Nevada, 11 June 1884 (7.5 [B.376])
  - "Yes, Charley…" Memo, 12 June 1884 (7.6 [B.377])
  - "Dear Charley…" Elmira, 24 June 1884 (7.7 [B.378])
  - NY-Letter from CLW, "Dear Uncle Sam,", 25 June 1884 (7.8 [B.379])
  - "Dear Charley…", July 1, 1884 (7.9 [B.380])
  - "Dear Charley…", July 2, 1884 (7.10 [B.381])
  - "Dear Charley…", 5 July 1884 (7.11 [B.382])
  - "Dear Charley…", 5 July 1884 (7.12 [B.383])
  - "Dear Charley…", 6 July 1884 (7.13[B.384])
  - Letter to unidentified correspondent, 10 July 1884 (7.14 [B.385])
  - "Dear Charley…", 10 July 1884 (7.15 [B.386])
  - "Dear Charlie and Annie …" Elmira, 10 July 1884 (7.16 [B.387])
  - "Dear Charley…", 10 July 1884 (7.17 [B.388])
  - "Dear Charley…" Elmira, 11 July 1884 (7.18 [B.389])
  - "Dear Charley…", 13 July 1884 (7.19 [B.390])
  - "Dear Charley…", 13 July 1884 (7.20 [B.391])
  - "Dear Charley…", 15 July 1884 (7.21 [B.392])
  - "Dear Charley…", 17 July 1884 (7.22 [B.393])
  - "Dear Charley…", 22 July 1884 (7.23 [B.394])
  - "Dear Charley…", 1884 (7.24 [B.395])
  - "Dear Charley…" Elmira, 24 July 1884 (7.25 [B.396])
  - Notes: First hand Prince and Pauper to Mallery, 1884 (7.26 [B.397])
  - "Dear Charley…", 7 Aug 1884 (7.27 [B.398])
  - "Dear Charley…", 11 Aug 1884 (7.28 [B.399])
  - "Dear Charley…", 14 Aug 1884 (7.29 [B.400])
  - "Dear Charley…" Elmira, 16 Aug 1884 (7.30 [B.401])
  - "Dear Charley…", 19 Aug 1884 (7.31 [B.402])
  - Letter to unidentified correspondent, Elmira, 1 Sep 1884 (7.32 [B.403])
  - "Dear Charley…", 5 Sep 1884 (7.33 [B.404])
  - "Dear Charley…", 5 Sep 1884 (7.34 [B.405])
  - "Dear Charley…", 8 Sep 1884 (7.35 [B.406])
  - "Dear Charley…", 8 Sep 1884 (7.36 [B.407])
  - Notes for Printer, [1884?] (7.37 [B.408])
  - "Dear Charley…" Saturday P.M., 1884 (7.38 [B.409])
  - "Dear Charley…", 15 Sep 1884 (7.39 [B.410])
  - "Dear Charley…" Saturday – Elmira, 20 Sep 1884 (7.40 [B.411])
  - "Dear Charley…" Wednesday, 1884 (7.41 [B.412])
  - "Dear Charley…" Elmira, 9 Sep 1884 (7.42 [B.413])
  - "Dear Charley…", 1884 (7.43 [B.414])
  - "To Charley…", 1884; (1st page missing) (7.44 [B.415])
  - "Dear Charley…", 3 Oct 1884 (7.45 [B.416])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 31 Oct 1884 (7.46 [B.417])
  - "Dear Charley…", 31 Oct 1884 (7.47 [B.418])
  - "Dear Charley…", Oct 1884; (Telegram) (7.48 [B.419])
  - "My Dear Bro…", 3 Nov 1884 (7.49 [B.420])
  - "My Dear Bro…" Boston, 15 Nov 1884 (7.50 [B.421])
  - "Dear Charley…" Fort Erie, 10 Dec 1884 (7.51 [B.422])
  - "Dear Charley…" Grand Rapids, MI, 15 Dec 1884 (7.52 [B.423])
  - "Dear Charley…" Toledo, 15 Dec 1884 (7.53 [B.424])
  - Letter to unidentified correspondent, "Huckleberry Finn,", 1884 (7.54 [B.425])
  - "Dear Charley…", 22 Dec 1884 (7.55 [B.426])
  - "Circular" C.L. Webster and Co., Publishers of Mark Twain's later works, 1884 (7.56 [B.427])
  - "Dear Charley…", 1884; (Telegram) (7.57 [B.428])
  - "Dear Charley…", 23 Dec 1884; (Telegram) (7.58 [B.429])
  - "My Dear Bro…" Hartford, 26 Dec 1884 (7.59 [B.430])
  - General Sheridan, "Dear Sir…" Hartford, 26 Dec 1884 (7.60 [B.431])
  - "Dear Charley…" Pittsburgh, 28 Dec 1884 (7.61 [B.432])
  - "My Dear Bro…" Pittsburgh, 28 Dec 1885 (7.62 [B.433])
  - "My Dear Mother…" Danville, IL, 28 Dec 1884 (7.63 [B.434])
  - Letter to unidentified correspondent, 1884? (7.64 [B.435])
  - "Dear Charley…" Cincinnati, 4 Jan 1885 (7.65 [B.436])
  - "Dear Charley…", 10 Jan 1885 (7.66 [B.437])
  - "Dear Mollie…" Hartford, CT-Letter from Olivia l. Clemens, 11 Jan 1885 (7.67 [B.438])
  - Telegram to C.L. Webster, 13 Jan 1885 (7.68 [B.439])
  - "Dear Charley…" Keokuk, 15 Jan 1885 (7.69 [B.440])
  - "My Dear Bro…" Chicago, Friday morning, 1885 (7.70 [B.441])
  - "Dear Charley…", 1885 (7.71 [B.442])
  - "Dear Charley…", 19 Jan 1885 (7.72 [B.443])
  - "Dear Charley…" Janesville, 19 Jan 1885 (8.1 [B.444])
  - "Dear Charley…", 21 Jan 1885 (8.2 [B.445])
  - "Dear Charley…" St. Paul, 23 Jan 1885 (8.3 [B.446])
  - "Dear Charley…" St. Paul, 23 Jan 1885 (8.4 [B.447])
  - "Dear Charley…" St. Paul, 23 Jan 1885 (8.5 [B.448])
  - "Dear Charley…" Minneapolis, 25 Jan 1885 (8.6 [B.449])
  - "Dear Charley…" Minneapolis, 26 Jan 1885 (8.7 [B.450])
  - "Dear Charley…" On the train, 27 Jan 1885 (8.8 [B.451])
  - D Appleton Statement with SLC notation on it, 28 Jan 1885 (8.9 [B.452])
  - Telegram to C.L. Webster, 29 Jan 1885 (8.10 [B.453])
  - Webster- See fine notice…., 1885 (8.11 [B.454])
  - "Dear Charley…" Indianapolis, 8 Feb 1885 (8.12 [B.455])
  - "Dear Charley…" Columbus, 10 Feb 1885 (8.13 [B.456])
  - "Dear Charley…" Toronto, 15 Feb 1885 (8.14 [B.457])
  - "Dear Charley…" Brockton, 17 Feb 1885 (8.15 [B.458])
  - Letter to unidentified correspondent. "2 Leave 2 cloth Finn's at Everett House Monday afternoon,", 1885 (8.16 [B.459 ])
  - "Dear Bro…", Feb. 1885 (8.17 [B.460])
  - "Dear Charley…" Everett House, 1885 (8.18 [B.461])
  - "Dear Bro and Sister…" Hartford, 5 Mar 1885 (8.19 [B.462])
  - "Dear Charley…" 182 Center St. Hartford, 6 Mar 1885 (8.20 [B.463])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 13 Mar 1885 (8.21 [B.464])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 16 Mar 1885 (8.22 [B.465])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 4 Apr 1885 (8.23 [B.466])
  - "Dear Charley…", 4 Apr 1885 (8.24 [B.467])
  - Prefatory Remark: "Huckleberry Finn is not….", 1885 (8.25 [B.468])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, Sunday, 1885 (8.26 [B.469])
  - SLC to Dear Charley, Law Office of William Hamersley Hartford, 6 Apr 1885 (8.27 [B.470])
  - "P.S. Charley…", 6 Apr 1885 (8.28 [B.471])
  - "Dear Charley…", 8 Apr 1885 (8.29 [B.472])
  - "Dear Charley…" Sunday, 1885 (8.30 [B.473])
  - "Dear Charley…" Sunday, 1885 (8.31 [B.474])
  - "Dear Charley…", 1885 (8.32 [B.475])
  - "Dear Charley…", 11 Apr 1885 (8.33 [B.476])
  - "Dear Charley…", 11 Apr 1885 (8.34 [B.477])
  - "Dear Bro…", 11 Apr 1885 (8.35 [B.478])
  - "Dear Charley…" Friday Evening, 1885 (8.36 [B.479])
  - "Dear Charley…" Sunday, 1885 (8.37 [B.480])
  - "My Dear Sister…" Hartford, 15 Apr 1885 (8.38 [B.481])
  - P.S. I forgot…(To Charley), 1885 (8.39 [B.482])
  - "Dear Colonel Grant..." Letterhead of Charles L. Webster, 658 Broadway, NY, 30 Apr 1885 (8.40 [B.483])
  - "Dear Charley…", 5 May 1885 (8.41 [B.484])
  - Letter to Orion, Hartford, 5 May 1885 (8.42 [B.485])
  - "Dear Charlie…", 10 May 1885 (8.43 [B.486])
  - "Dear Charley…", 13 May 1885 (8.44 [B.487])
  - "Dear Bro…", 16 May 1885 (8.45 [B.488])
  - "Dear Charley…" Sunday, 1885 (8.46 [B.489])
  - The ABC Transliterations Bureau adv. with note in SLC's handwriting, 1885 (8.47 [B.490])
  - "To Whom It May Concern…" Charles L. Webster and Co. Letterhead, 27 May 1885 (8.48 [B.491])
  - "My Dear Bro…" Hartford, 22 May 1885 (8.49 [B.492])
  - "Dear Ma…" Everett House Union Square, 8 June 1885 (8.50 [B.493])
  - [Charles] Webster and Co. MEMO, 1885 (8.51 [B.494])
  - "Dear Sister…" Hartford, 12 June 1885 (8.52 [B.495])
  - "Dear Charley…" Elmira, Sunday, 1885 (8.53 [B.496])
  - "Dear Charley…", 17 June 1885 (8.54 [B.497])
  - "Dear Charley…" Elmira, 24 June 1885 (8.55 [B.498])
  - "Dear Ma…" Elmira, 26 June 1885 (8.56 [B.499])
  - Letter to unidentified correspondent, undated (8.57 [B.500])
  - Letter to unidentified correspondent, undated (8.58 [B.501])
  - Telegram [Charles] L. Webster, 27 July 1885 (8.59 [B.502])
  - "Dear Charley…" Elmira, 28 July 1885 (8.60 [B.503])
  - "Dear Charley…", 28 July 1885 (8.61 [B.504])
  - "Dear Charley-When you get to London…", 1885 (8.62 [B.505])
  - "My Dear Niece…" Elmira, 30 July 1885 (8.63 [B.506])
  - "Dear Molly…" Elmira, 6 Aug 1885 (no folder [B.507])
  - "Dear Sirs…" Elmira, Wednesday 5 p.m., 1885 (8.64 [B.508])
  - "My Dear Bro…" Hartford, 22 Sep 1885 (8.65 [B.509])
  - Copyright No. 21186 Q of letter from Gen. S.B. Buckner to Gen. U.S. Grant, 9 Oct 1885 (8.66 [B.510])
  - Copyright Office-receipt for 2 copies of a facsimile of Bucknew to Grant Letter, 1885 (8.67 [B.511])
  - "Dear Charley…", 13 Oct 1885 (8.68 [B.512])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 22 Oct 1885 (8.69 [B.513])
  - "Dear Charlie and Annie…" Letter from Olivia L. Clemens, 25 Oct 1885 (8.70 [B.514])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 28 Oct 1885 (9.1 [B.515])
  - "Dear Annie…" Hartford, 28 Oct 1885 (9.2 [B.516])
  - "Dear Charley…" Tuesday, 1885 (9.3 [B.517])
  - "Dear Ma…" Hartford, 30 Oct 1885 (9.4 [B.518])
  - "Dear Charley…", 30 Oct 1885 (9.5 [B.519])
  - "Dear Charley…", 2 Nov 1885 (9.6 [B.520])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 10 Nov 1885 (9.7 [B.521])
  - To the Editor of the Sun…Signed: D. Wahrheit, 1885 (9.8 [B.522])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 11 Nov 1885 (9.9 [B.523])
  - "Dear Charley…", 1885 (9.10 [B.524])
  - "Dear Charley…", 6 Dec 1885 (no folder [B.525])
  - "Dear Charley…" Wednesday, 16 Dec 1885 (9.11 [B.526])
  - "Dear Charley…" 6 pm, 16 Dec 1885 (9.12 [B.527])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 17 Dec 1885 (9.13 [B.528])
  - "Dear Ma…" Hartford, 18 Dec 1885 (9.14 [B.529])
  - "Dear Charley…" Private, Hartford, 18 Dec 1885 (9.15 [B.530])
  - "Dear Charley…", 26 Dec 1885 (9.16 [B.531])
  - "Dear Charley…", 21 Dec 1885 (9.17 [B.532])
  - "Dear Charley…", 28 Dec 1885 (9.18 [B.533])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 29 Dec 1885 (9.19 [B.534])
  - "Dear Charley…" Saturday, 1855 (9.20 [B.535A])
  - "Dear Charley…", 3 Jan 1886 (9.21 [B.535B])
  - "Dear Charley…", 13 Jan 1886 (9.22 [B.536])
  - "Dear Charley…" Sunday, 1 Feb 1886 (9.23 [B.537])
  - "Dear Charley…", 8 Feb 1886 (9.24 [B.538])
  - "Dear Charley…", 8 Feb 1886 (9.25 [B.539])
  - "Dear Charley…", 10 Feb 1886 (9.26 [B.540])
  - "Dear Charley…", 13 Feb 1886 (9.27 [B.541])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 19 Mar 1886 (9.28 [B.542])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 27 Mar 1886 (9.29 [B.543])
  - "Dear Charlie…" Hartford, Conn.- Letter from Olivia L. Clemens, 1886 (9.30 [B.544])
  - "Dear Charley…", 6 Apr 1886 (9.31 [B.545])
  - "Dear Charley…", 12 Apr 1886 (9.32 [B.546])
  - "Dear Charley…", 26 Apr 1886 (9.33 [B.547])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 22 Apr 1886 (9.34 [B.548])
  - "Dear Charley…", 25 May 1886; (Telegram) (9.35 [B.549])
  - "Dear Charley…" Book Order, Hartford, 22 Apr 1886 (9.36 [B.550])
  - "Dear Charley…", 3 June 1886 (9.37 [B.551])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 6 June 1886 (9.38 [B.552])
  - "Dear Charley…", 11 June 1886 (9.39 [B.553])
  - "Dear Charley…" Elmira, 17 June 1886 (9.40 [B.554])
  - "Dear Charley-I have attempted no answer…", 1886 (9.41 [B.555])
  - Fragment of letter to sister, Pamela C. Moffett, 1886 (9.42 [B.556])
  - "Dear Charley…" Elmira, 6 Aug 1886 (9.43 [B.557])
  - "Dear Molly…" Elmira, 6 Aug 1886 (9.44 [B.557A])
  - "Dear Ma…" Elmira, 7 Aug 1886 (9.45 [B.558])
  - "Dear Mr. Hall…" Elmira, 25 Aug 1886 (9.46 [B.559])
  - "Dear Charley…", 3 Sep 1886 (9.47 [B.560])
  - "Dear Charley…" Murray Hill Hotel, NY, 5 Oct 1886 (9.48 [B.561])
  - "Dear Charley…", 10 Oct 1886 (9.49 [B.562])
  - "Dear Annie…" Hartford, 18 Oct 1886 (9.50 [B.563])
  - "Dear Charley…" Sheridan Book, Hartford, 13 Nov 1886 (9.51 [B.564])
  - "Dear Charley…" In relation to Henry Clews, Hartford, 17 Nov 1886 (9.52 [B.565])
  - Hartford-Telegram to [Charles] L. Webster, 17 Nov 1886 (9.53 [B.566])
  - "Dear Sirs…" Hartford- [Charles] L. Webster and Co., 29 Nov 1886 (9.54 [B.567])
  - "Dear Charley- Don't forget…", 6 Dec 1886 (9.55 [B.567A])
  - "Dear Charley…", 11 Dec 1886 (9.56 [B.568])
  - "Dear Charley- I want to bother you…", Dec 1885 (9.57 [B.568A])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford- Letter from Olivia L. Clemens, 1886 (9.58 [B.569])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 14 Dec 1885 (9.59 [B.570])
  - "P.S. Livy wants you…", 26 Dec 1886 (9.60 [B.571])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 26 Dec 1886 (9.61 [B.572])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 30 Dec, 1886 (9.62 [B.573])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 13 Jan 1887 (9.63 [B.574])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 19 Jan 1887 (9.64 [B.575])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 15 Feb 1887 (9.65 [B.576])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 25 Feb 1887 (9.66 [B.577])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 1 Mar 1887 (9.67 [B.578])
  - "Dear Bro…" Hartford, 16 Mar 1887 (9.68 [B.579])
  - "Dear Charley…", 28 Mar 1887 (10.1 [B.580])
  - Telegram to [Charles] L. Webster, 28 Mar 1887 (10.2 [B.581])
  - "My Dear Sister…" Hartford, 2 Apr 1887 (10.3 [B.582])
  - Telegram to [Charles] L. Webster, 4 Apr 1887 (10.4 [B.583])
  - "Dear Charley…", 17 Apr 1887 (10.5 [B.584])
  - "Dear Charley…", 22 Apr 1887 (10.6 [B.585])
  - Letter for SLC written by F. Whitman, 28 Apr 1887 (10.7 [B.586])
  - "Dear Charley…", 9 May 1887 (10.8 [B.587])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 11 May 1887 (10.9 [B.588])
  - "Dear Charley…" Hartford, 25 May 1887 (10.10 [B.589])
  - "Dear Charley…", 28 May 1887 (10.11 [B.590])
  - "Dear Mr. Hall…" Elmira, 9 July 1887 (10.12 [B.591])
  - "My Dear Sister…" Elmira, 12 July 1887 (10.13 [B.592])
  - "Dear Ma…" Elmira, 24 July 1887 (10.14 [B.593])
  - "Dear Charley…" Home, Sept 5, 1887 (10.15 [B.594])
  - Envelope addressed to C.L. Webster by SLC, 9 Sep 1887 (10.16 [B.595])